

EDUCATION

Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology (2009 -2014)

• Location: Hanoi

• Major: Information Technology

Subjects: Data structure,
 Algorithm, OOP, Software
 Development Process, Mobile
 Development, Web Development,
 Database Management,
 Distributed Systems

• GPA: 8.0 / 10

Thanglong Aptech (2012 - 2013)

Location: *Hanoi*Course: *ACCPi*

• Subjects: Web Dev, Java, .NET,
Asp

SKILLS

- OOP, Functional Programming
- Java, Springframework, JPA, Hibernate, Srping Data, Primefaces
- Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpresJS
- Python, Django
- MySQL, MongoDB, Redis, ElasticSearch
- Microservice, RESTful API

DAO VAN KHUONG

software developer

PERSONAL PROFILE

My fullname is Dao Van Khuong. I come from Hanoi, Vietnam. I have been working as a software developer for more than 5 years.

Java is my major programming language. In 2014, I became an "Oracle Certified Professional Java SE6 Programmer"

For a long time, I worked with Java and its popular frameworks: *PrimeFaces*, *Jersey*, *Hibernate*, *Springframework* (*Springboot as well*)

Beside Java and its ecosystem, I also work with frontend stuffs: *ReactJS*, *React Native*, *Native Android Development*

WORK EXPERIENCE

I. Frontend Developer at Vietnam Prosperity Bank (2017 - Present)

What I do:

- Work with Project Owner and Designer to finalize the designs for User App and Administration App
- Develop frontend side of both User App and Admin App, integrate with backend API as well
- Apply changes to the projects to improve performance and UI

What I learn:

- Learn new things about banking sector and some products of the bank
- Learn Python (actually Django) to build the Blog module for the User App mentioned above

Technologies used in the project:

• ReactJS, Django, Springboot, MySQL

II. Backend Developer at FPTSoftware Co. (2016 - 2017)

What I do:

- Develop API for the frontend side, propose improments for the backend side
- Daily meeting with client to discuss business changes or new features
- Teach other guys in the department Android development

What I learn:

- Learn to conduct a meeting with oversea client via Skype
- Learn to code and teach others to code

Technologies used in the project:

• AngularJS, Jersey, MongoDB, iText

III. Software Developer at Viettel Software Center (2014 - 2016)

What I do:

- Develop features assigned by the leader (Both frontend and backend side)
- Do weekly code-review with team
- Propose changes to improve the project

What I learn:

- Learn the big database schema of a big company
- Learn the Spring framework and Primefaces framework